<?xml version="1.0"?>
<dialogue>
	<perogi>
		<greeting>Yes, hi. Welcome to @shitflix/@. Things are a little bare right now because everyone got @kidnapped/@ by the @NSA/@.</greeting>
		<invalid>I have no strong feelings on that subject.</invalid>
		<nsa>They are the bad guys. They arrested a bunch of us for doing illegal things. Only me and toast were @not kidnapped/@.</nsa>
		<perogi>What? You just want me to tell you everything about myself? If you want to get to know my character you're going to have to do more than just fucking ask me about myself. Honestly.</perogi>
		<toast>Toast is pretty cool. He doesn't do much really. In case you haven't noticed, he communicates using only pictures of cats.</toast>
		<notkidnapped>Yeah Toast and I are the only ones who didn't get taken by the NSA. Dunno why, probably because neither of us really do much, let alone illegal things.</notkidnapped>
		<tor>Tor is fantastic. I love the idea of cryptography. Specifically how it takes power away from centralized authorities, and can empower decentralized organizations. That's like, paradigm raping shit right there.</tor>
		<shitflix>Yes that is this place. I fucking love it here it is fantastic. I won't go into all the wishy-washy philosophical reasons, because those aren't really important anyway. This is just a wonderful place to get drunk or high and watch really bad movies with cool people.</shitflix>
		<kidnapped>Yeah the NSA was spying on us and eventually got most of the 420streamers arrested. You should go find them, you'd probably want a @guide/@ though.</kidnapped>
		<guide>Me? No I'm not going to be your guide. I made this game so that really wouldn't be fair if I just told you everything, would it? Just go find Howlie, he'll probably be your guide. He's imprisoned somewhere on the internet, in @Reddit/@ I think. Just go to Reddit and try asking people about the NSA or howlie.</guide>
		<reddit>Yes Reddit, it's this awful place on the internet that I hate. Oh you mean how do you get there? Oh that's right, you need to know the appropriate links to get places. Here's the link to Reddit. From here go to the internet backbone, and from there you can get to Reddit. Now please leave, I am very busy drinking and watching television.</reddit>
	</perogi>
	<toast>
		<greeting>Toast holds up a picture of a cat. The cat is waving.</greeting>
		<invalid>Toast holds up a picture of a cat. The cat is confused.</invalid>
	</toast>
</dialogue>
